Guide to the Beyond the Pale Records TAM.718
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Hanukkah Show with Tamara Cohen, Matt McDonald, and Leslie Cagan [2000-073], 2000-12-24; cuid34145 (Box 14, Audiocassette 718_0509)
  Duration: 1:01:03, Preservation Note: Digital Errors During Program; Static During Program
  Duplicate of 718_0286
- Ocean Hill-Brownsville, Thirty Years Later [2000-17], 2000-12-26; cuid34146 (Box 8, Audiocassette 718_0280)
  Duration: 1:55:57, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times
  Related to 718_0152, 718_0199, 718_0414, 718_0415, 718_0263, 718_0427, 718_0432
- 30 Years After Ocean Hill, Reel 1 [1998-054], 2000-12-26; cuid2612 (Box 34, Item 718_1002, Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_610)
  30 Years after Oceanhill-Brownsville
  Original Format: 1/4" Open Reel Audio, Duration: 67 min.
- 30 Years After Ocean Hill, Reel 2 [1998-053], 2000-12-26; cuid2611 (Box 34, Item 718_1001, Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_609)
  30 Years after Ocean Hill
  Original Format: 1/4" Open Reel Audio, Duration: 37 min.
- A: Rabab Abdelhadi on Israel/Palestine conflict; Jewish Film Festival with Jim Hoberman and Aviva Weintraub / B: Excerpt from The Moment of the Wandering Jew; Ben Shahn photo Exhibition; Nan Rubin and Lynn Gumbert of NYU Grey Gallery; Jennifer Bleyer with Susan Douglas and Hyang Lee [2001-061], 2000 December 31; 2001 January 1; cuid34147 (Box 9, Audiocassette 718_0310)
  Duration: 2:02:41, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times
  Duplicate of 718_0505, 718_0522
- Ben Shahn Photo Exhibition; Lower East Side Housing; Excerpt from The Moments of the Wandering Jew [2000-069], 2000-12-31; cuid34148 (Box 14, Audiocassette 718_0505)
  Duration: 1:00:50, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times; Program is Only in Right Channel from 17:31 to 18:09
  Duplicate of 718_0310
- Jewish Film Festival [2001-0105], cuid34149 (Box 21, Reel 718_0951)
  Duration: 0:11:01, Preservation Note: Static During Program; Program Distorted at Times
- The Flashpoints, Collection of Poems by Aurora Levins-Morales [2015-007], circa 2001 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_604)
- Rabbi Arthur Waskow: Sukkot Reflections on WTC Attacks [2001-0104], cuid34150 (Box 21, Reel 718_0950)
  Duration: 0:10:30, Preservation Note: Static During Program; Program Distorted at Times
- Israel: Tel Aviv Protests, Netivot, Marilyn Kleinberg Neimark in Tel Aviv, Hotline for Migrant Workers, Part 1, 2001 January - February (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_294)
- Israel: Dalit Baum Who Profits?, Jaffa Housing Crisis, Weitzman School, Part 2, 2001 January - February (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_295)
- Theater and Social Change [2001-0181], 2001-01-02; cuid34151 (Box 10, Audiocassette 718_0328)
  Duration: 1:34:47, Preservation Note: Clicks and Pops During Program; Program Distorted at Times
- Aviva Weintraub on Jewish Film Festival; Kathleen Blee on Inside Organized Racism [2001-0142], 2001-01-06; cuid34152 (Box 15, Audiocassette 718_0550)
  Duration: 0:58:00, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times; Static During Program; Program Recorded at a Very High Level at Times
  Duplicate of 718_0954, 718_0302
- Rabab Abdulhadi on Middle East; Jim Hoberman and Aviva Weintraub on Jewish Film Festival [2001-0114], 2001-01-07; cuid34153 (Box 14, Audiocassette 718_0522)
  Duration: 1:01:14, Preservation Note: Digital Errors and Dropouts During Program
- A: Jerrold Nadler on the new congress; Robert Jackson on Campaign for Fiscal Equity's public education lawsuit / B: Elliot Mincberg on John Ashcroft, Mosco Boucault on Terrorists in Retirement; Jennifer Bleyer on J20 protest at Bush's inaugural [2001-0178], 2001 September 14; 2001 September 21; cuid34154 (Box 10, Audiocassette 718_0325)
  Duration: 2:00:20, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times; Echo During Program
  Duplicate of 718_0526, 718_0523
- Rep. Jerrold Nadler on New Congress; Robert Jackson on Landmark Court Decision [2001-0118], 2001-01-14; cuid34155 (Box 14, Audiocassette 718_0526)
  Duration: 0:58:57, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times
  Duplicate of 718_0325
- Mosco Boucault on Terrorists in Retirement; Elliot Mincberg on John Ashcroft; Jennifer Bleyer on J20 Protest [2001-0115], 2001-01-21; cuid34156 (Box 14, Audiocassette 718_0523)
  Duration: 1:00:15, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times
- A: Jerome Segal, Michel Warschawski, Edison and NYC Schools / B: Alan Levine on Chavas, Joe Conn on Bush's faith initiative, hannah Saffron on Israeli elections [2001-058], 2001 January 28; 2001 February 4; cuid34157 (Box 9, Audiocassette 718_0307)
  Duration: 1:51:50, Preservation Note: Side B is Mono; Program Distorted at Times; Static During Program; Phasing During Program
  Duplicate of 718_0524, 718_0525
- Jerome Segal on Bush and Middle East; Michel Warschawski on Upcoming Elections; Andy Stettner and Sandra Rivers on Edison School Takeover of 5 Failing Schools (Partial) [2001-0116], 2001-01-28; cuid34158 (Box 14, Audiocassette 718_0524)
  Duration: 0:51:03, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times; Program Recorded at a Very High Level; High Background Noise During Program
  Duplicate of 718_0307, 718_0525
- Alice Kessler-Harris Interview on Anzia Yezierska, author of Bread Givers and "The Open Cage" [2001-0206], 2001-02-02; cuid34159 (Box 22, Reel 718_0955)
  Duration: 0:20:49, Preservation Note: Phasing During Program
- Charas Court Battle; Bush's Faith Initiative; Current Israeli Politics [2001-0117], 2001-02-04; cuid34160 (Box 14, Audiocassette 718_0525)
  Duration: 0:57:27, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times
  Duplicate of 718_0307, 718_0524
- A: Richard Cohen, The Avengers; Gila Svirsky on Sharon, Israeli left / B: Critical Resistance conference: Jennifer Bleyer, Kate Rhee, Shayna; Melanie Kaye/Kantrowitz on Pacifica Meeting; Mary Lowenthal Felstiner on Charlotte Salomon's Book Life? or Theatre? [2001-0174], 2001 February 11; 2001 March 4; cuid34161 (Box 10, Audiocassette 718_0321)
  Duration: 1:56:19, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times; Phasing During Program; No Left Channel From 00:30:28 Until End of Program on Side A During Program
  Duplicate of 718_0540, 718_0539, 718_0952
- Rich Cohen on The Avengers; Gila Svirsky on Ariel Sharon and the Israeli Left [2001-0132], 2001-02-11; cuid34162 (Box 15, Audiocassette 718_0540)
  Duration: 0:59:54, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times
  Duplicate of 718_0321
- Marathon 2 hour [2001-0173], 2001-02-18; cuid34163 (Box 10, Audiocassette 718_0320)
  Tape is Completely Blank - No Digital Files Created
- Marathon Special: Phyllis Bennis on Iraqi Sanctions; Michel Warschawski on Israel/Palestine; Naomi Klein on No Logo [2001-0129], 2001-02-18; cuid34164 (Box 15, Audiocassette 718_0537)
  Duration: 1:59:53, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times; Phasing During Program; Program Recorded at a Very High Level; Digital Errors During Program
- Critical Resistance Conference; Pacifica Board Meeting; Mary Lowenthal Felstiner on To Paint Her Life: Charlotte Salomon [2001-0131], 2001-03-04; cuid34165 (Box 15, Audiocassette 718_0539)
  Duration: 1:00:07, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times; Digital Errors During Program
  Duplicate of 718_0321, 718_0952
- Mary Lowenthal Felstiner Interview with Melanie Kaye/Kantrowitz on Charlotte Salomon Biography, To Paint Her Life, 2001-03-04; cuid34166 (Box 22, Reel 718_0952)
  Duration: 0:22:18, Preservation Note: Static During Program; Program Distorted at Times
  Duplicate of 718_0539, 718_0321
- A: Abe Beam's legacy with Chris McNickle To Be Mayor of New York; The Marc Rich pardon with Rachel Donadio and Rabbi Mordechai Liebling / B: Bob Ganji on "Drop the Rock" campaign; Ella Shohat, Inderpal Grewal, and Caren Kaplan on Talking Visions: Multicultural Feminism in a Transnational Age [2001-0172], 2001 March 11; 2001 March 18; cuid34167 (Box 10, Audiocassette 718_0319)
  Duration: 2:01:54, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times; Static During Program
  Duplicate of 718_0520, 718_0519
- Abe Beam's Legacy; Marc Rich Pardon [2001-0112], 2001-03-11; cuid34168 (Box 14, Audiocassette 718_0520)
  Duration: 1:00:37, Preservation Note: Digital Errors During Program
  Duplicate of 718_0319, 718_0519
- Hasia Diner on Women, Culture, and Food [2001-0204], 2001-03-13; cuid34169 (Box 22, Reel 718_0953)
  Duration: 0:17:12, Preservation Note: Broken Splices Repaired; Program Distorted at Times
  Duplicate of 718_0557
- Rockefeller Drug Law Repeal; Multicultural Feminism [2001-0111], 2001-03-18; cuid34170 (Box 14, Audiocassette 718_0519)
  Duration: 1:00:58, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times
  Duplicate of 718_0319, 718_0520
- A: Sam Friedman in Conversation with Jeremy Burton and Melanie Kaye/Kantrowitz, Hasia Diner on Jewish Women and Food / B: Confederacy Supporters in the Bush Administration; Alice Kessler Harris on Anzia Yezierska [2001-059], 2001-03-25; 2001-04-01; cuid2617 (Box 9, Item 718_0308, Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_615)
  Sam Freedman author of Jew vs. Jew: The Struggle for the Soul of American Jewry, with Melanie Kaye/Kantrowitz and Jeremy Burton; Nan Rubin interviews Hasia Diner on Jewish women and food. Chip Berlet, Political Research Associates, on pro-Confederacy sentiments in the Bush administration, Robert Rosen, author of The Jewish Confederates (University of South Carolina Press), co-host Nan Rubin, Harriet Tanzman interviews Alice Kessler Harris on Anzia Yezierska, author of The Bread Giver.
- Sam Friedman on Jew v. Jew; Hasia Diner on Jewish Women and Food [2001-0149], 2001-03-25; cuid34171 (Box 15, Audiocassette 718_0557)
  Duration: 0:58:30, Preservation Note: Digital Errors During Program
  Duplicate of 718_0953
- Jews and the Confederacy: Chip Berlet on Pro-Confederacy Sentiments in the Bush Administration and Robert Rosen on The Jewish Confederates; Alice Kessler-Harris Interview on Anzia Yezierska [2001-0122], 2001-04-01; cuid2608 (Box 14, Item 718_0530, Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_607)
  Chip Berlet, Political Research Associates, on pro-Confederacy sentiments in the Bush administration, Robert Rosen, author of The Jewish Confederates (University of South Carolina Press), co-host Nan Rubin, Harriet Tanzman interviews Alice Kessler Harris on Anzia Yezierska, author of The Bread Giver.
  Original Format: DAT, Duration: 64 min.
- A: Jonathan Rosen The Talmud and the Internet; Sandra Rivers and Sarah Eisenstein on The Fight against Edison [2001-0175], 2001 April 8; 2001 April 15; cuid34172 (Box 10, Audiocassette 718_0322)
  Duration: 1:00:23, Preservation Note: Side B is Blank; Program Distorted at Times
  Title may not reflect content
- Jonathan Rosen on The Talmud and the Internet; the Edison School Vote with Sara Eisenstein and Sandra Rivers [2001-0120], 2001-04-08; cuid34173 (Box 14, Audiocassette 718_0528)
  Duration: 0:59:28
  Duplicate of 718_0947
- A: Sam Friedman in conversation with Jeremy burton and Melanie Kaye/Kantrowitz, Hasia Diner on Jewish women and food / B: Confederacy Supporters in the Bush Administration, Alice Kessler Harris on Anzia Yezierska [2001-059], 2001-04-15; cuid34174 (Box 14, Audiocassette 718_0529)
  Duration: 0:59:11
- A: Gila Svirsky, Kevin Feinberg, Marc Cooper on L.A. Mayoral Race / B: Ilan Stavans on Latino-Jewish identity; Donna Nevels and Amy Velez; Jeremy Burton on Jewish community relation to Latino community [2001-0183], 2001 April 22; 2001 April 29; cuid34175 (Box 10, Audiocassette 718_0330)
  Duration: 2:01:20, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times; Static During Program; High Amount of Hiss During Program
  Duplicate of 718_0527, 718_0531, 718_0946
- Gila Svirsky; Kevin Feinberg on "Facing History" Holocaust Education; Marc Cooper on L.A. Mayoral Elections [2001-0123], 2001-04-22; cuid34176 (Box 14, Audiocassette 718_0531)
  Duration: 1:02:03, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times; Overlapping Content from 1:01:46 to 1:01:54
  Duplicate of 718_0527, 718_0330, 718_0946
- Ilan Stavans, Amy Velez, Donna Nevel, and Jeremy Burton on Latin/Jewish Identity and Latino-Jewish Relations [2001-0119], 2001-04-29; cuid34177 (Box 14, Audiocassette 718_0527)
  Duration: 1:00:32, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times
  Duplicate of 718_0531, 718_0330, 718_0946
- Crystal Quilt, Disk 1 [2001-0194], 2001-04-29 (Box 18, Item 718_0664)
- Crystal Quilt with Sherry Gorelick, Esther Lederman, and Tamar Katriel, Disk 2 [2001-0191], 2001-04-29 (Box 18, Item 718_0665)
- Ilan Stavans on Latino/Jewish Identity [2001-0100], 2001-04-29; cuid34178 (Box 21, Reel 718_0946)
  Duration: 0:19:37, Preservation Note: Broken Splices Repaired
  Duplicate of 718_0527, 718_0531, 718_0330
- Jewish Unity for a Just Peace Conference: Jeff Halper (Tracks 2-3), Rela Mazali (Track 4), and Irena Klepfisz (Track 1) [2001-0195], 2001-05-04-2001-05-06 (Box 18, Item 718_0668)
- Jewish Unity for a Just Peace Conference (Continued): Rela Mazali and Ali Abunimah [2001-0196], 2001-05-05 (Box 18, Item 718_0669)
- Marilyn Kleinberg Neimark and Marsha Triedman on Chicago Jewish Peace Conference; Lois Cronholm and Leon Botstein on the Center for Jewish History; Mellish on Joey Ramone [2001-056], 2001-05-06; cuid34179 (Box 9, Audiocassette 718_0305)
  Duration: 0:58:04, Preservation Note: Side B is Blank; Static During Program; Program Distorted at Times; Speed Fluctuation at Start of Program on Side A During Program
  Duplicate of 718_0516, 718_0329
- Lower East Side 5 [2001-0182], 2001-05-06; cuid34180 (Box 10, Audiocassette 718_0329)
  Duration: 0:57:35, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times; Static During Program
  Duplicate of 718_0305, 718_0516
- Jewish Peace Conference; Center for Jewish History; Joey Ramone Tribute [2001-0108], 2001-05-06; cuid34181 (Box 14, Audiocassette 718_0516)
  Duration: 0:57:04, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times
  Duplicate of 718_0305, 718_0329
- A: Karen Wheeler on Horowitz Ad, Rabbi Sharon Kleinbaum and Jeremy Burton, Amos on slavery reparations, Lee Cokorinos on sanctity of human life conference / B: Gila Svirsky on June 8 Women in Black vigils, Judith Sloan and Warren Lehrer on multi-racial, multi-ethnic Queens [2001-055], 2001 May 13; 2001 June 1; cuid34182 (Box 9, Audiocassette 718_0304)
  Duration: 1:59:01, Preservation Note: Side B is Stereo; Program Distorted at Times
  Duplicate of 718_0515, 718_0949, 718_0548
- Slavery Reparations; The Sanctity of Human Life Conference [2001-0107], 2001-05-13; cuid34183 (Box 14, Audiocassette 718_0515)
  Duration: 1:00:46, Preservation Note: High Background Noise During Program; Program Distorted at Times
  Duplicate of 718_0304, 718_0949
- Rabbi Sharon Kleinbaum on Reparations [2001-0103], 2001-05-13; cuid34184 (Box 21, Reel 718_0949)
  Duration: 0:12:00, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times
  Duplicate of 718_0304, 718_0515
- Allen Ginsberg Special, 2001-06-03; cuid34185 (Box 9, Audiocassette 718_0303)
  Duplicate of 718_0560 and 718_0521; Related to 718_0930; Features a 6-minute clip from 718_0930
- Allen Ginsberg Special with Co-host Janet Coleman, Part 2 [2001-0113], 2001-06-03; cuid34186 (Box 14, Audiocassette 718_0521)
  Duration: 0:58:12, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times; Digital Errors During Program
  Duplicate of 718_0303; Related to 718_0560
- Allen Ginsberg Special with Co-host Janet Coleman, Part 1, 2001-06-03; cuid34187 (Box 15, Audiocassette 718_0560)
  Duration: 1:01:43, Preservation Note: Static During Program; Program Distorted at Times
  Duplicate of 718_0303; Related to 718_0521 and 718_0930; Features a six-minute clip from 718_0930
- JFREJ Anti-Arab Racism Workshop, Panel 1 with Sam Husseini, Ella Shohat, and Steven Cohen [2001-0193], 2001-06-03 (Box 18, Item 718_0667)
- Gila Svirsky on June 8th Solidarity Vigils with Women in Black; Warren Lehrer and Judith Sloan on Crossing the BLVD [2001-0140], 2001-06-10; cuid34188 (Box 15, Audiocassette 718_0548)
  Duration: 0:59:00, Preservation Note: Digital Errors During Program; Program Distorted at Times; Program in Silence from 38:50 to 40:24
  Duplicate of 718_0304
- A: James Tisch, AIDS March, Bruni Burris, Human Rights Watch Film Festival / B: Gay Pride Show [2001-057], 2001 June 17; 2001 June 24; cuid34189 (Box 9, Audiocassette 718_0306)
  Duration: 1:59:06, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times; Static During Program
  Duplicate of 718_0518, 718_0517
- James Tisch United Jewish Communities (UJC) Chair Nomination; AIDS March; Human Rights Watch Film Festival [2001-0110], 2001-06-17; cuid34190 (Box 14, Audiocassette 718_0518)
  Duration: 0:57:58, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times; Digital Errors During Program
  Duplicate of 718_0306
- Gay Pride Show: Circus Amok with Jennifer Miller and Jenny Romaine and Schmear the Queer Zine with Scott Barry and Brian Kay [2001-0109], 2001-06-24; cuid34191 (Box 14, Audiocassette 718_0517)
  Duration: 0:58:53, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times; Digital Errors During Program
- A: Marc Berenson on Lori Berenson; Doris Boskey on Gidone Busch; Leslie Kagan on Pacifica / B: Joan Schenkar on Truly Wilde: The Unsettling Story of Dolly Wilde, Oscar's Unusual Niece; Chip Berlet on the Protocols of the Elders of Zion and Rule by Secrecy [2001-0170], 2001 July 1; 2001 July 8; cuid34192 (Box 10, Audiocassette 718_0317)
  Duration: 1:58:58, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times; Echo During Program
  Duplicate of 718_0331, 718_0555, 718_0553
- Mark Berenson on Lori Berenson; Doris Busch Boskey on Gidone Busch; Leslie Cagan on Pacifica/BAI [2001-0184], 2001-07-01; cuid34193 (Box 10, Audiocassette 718_0331)
  Duration: 0:57:54, Preservation Note: Side B is Blank; Program Distorted at Times; Static During Program; Echo During Program
  Duplicate of 718_0317, 718_0555
- Mark Berenson on Lori Berenson; Doris Boskey on Gidone Busch; Leslie Cagan on Pacifica [2001-0147], 2001-07-01; cuid34194 (Box 15, Audiocassette 718_0555)
  Duplicate of 718_0317, 718_0331
- Joan Schenkar on Truly Wilde; Chip Berlet on Protocols of the Elders of Zion and Rule by Secrecy [2001-0145], 2001-07-08; cuid34195 (Box 15, Audiocassette 718_0553)
  Duration: 0:58:37, Preservation Note: Digital Errors During Program; Program Distorted at Times
  Duplicate of 718_0317, 718_0948
- Joan Schenkar on Truly Wilde [2001-0102], 2001-07-08; cuid34196 (Box 21, Reel 718_0948)
  Duration: 0:21:51
  Duplicate of 718_0317, 718_0553
- A: Two talks from May 5-6 2001 conference: Jeff Halpern and Rela Mazali / B: Mike Wishnie on Supreme Court decisions on immigration; Chuck Zlatkin and Ellis Henican on efforts to save WEVD [2001-0167], 2001 July 29; 2001 July 15; cuid34197 (Box 9, Audiocassette 718_0315)
  Duration: 1:55:37, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times; No Left Channel From 00:32:27 Until 00:53:30 on Side A During Program; Static During Program
  Duplicate of 718_0552
- Mike Wishnie on Immigration; Chuck Zlatkin and Ellis Henican on WEVD [2001-0144], 2001-07-15; cuid34198 (Box 15, Audiocassette 718_0552)
  Duration: 0:56:18, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times
  Duplicate of 718_0315
- A: Liz Ritter, District 7 City Council Race; India and Israel with Aniruddha Das, Vijay Prashad, and Shubh Mathur / B: Arkady Kagan on District 47 council race; Eva Kollisch on Girl, in Movement; Leslie Cagan on Pacifica [2001-0168], 2001 August 5; 2001 July 22; cuid34199 (Box 10, Audiocassette 718_0316)
  Duration: 1:59:10, Preservation Note: Side B is Mono; Program Distorted at Times
  Duplicate of 718_0514, 718_0546
- Arkady Kagan in Brooklyn Council Race; Eva Kollisch on Girl In Movement; Leslie Cagan on Pacifica [2001-0106], 2001-07-22; cuid34200 (Box 14, Audiocassette 718_0514)
  Duration: 0:58:20, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times
  Duplicate of 718_0316
- Junity Conference [2001-0176], 2001-07-29; cuid34201 (Box 10, Audiocassette 718_0323)
- Jeff Halpern and Rela Magala Talks from Jewish Unity for a Just Peace Conference [2001-0146], 2001-07-29; cuid34202 (Box 15, Audiocassette 718_0554)
  Duration: 0:58:46, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times; Digital Errors During Program
- Liz Ritter on District 7 City Council Race; India and Israel with Aniruddha Das, Shubh Mathur, and Vijay Prashad [2001-0138], 2001-08-05; cuid34203 (Box 15, Audiocassette 718_0546)
  Duration: 0:59:32, Preservation Note: Static During Program
- Falastin Ismael, Director of Ilan; Maria de Pina, Human Resources Director of I'Lam [2001-0190], 2001-08-08 (Box 18, Item 718_0663)
- Jafar Farah of Mossawa Center [2001-0198], 2001-08-09 (Box 18, Item 718_0671)
- A: Dmitry Salita and Jimmy O.; Candidate interview Bronx Borough President Fernando Ferrer / B: Candidate interview Public Advocate Mark Greene; Grady Turner, curator of "Flophouse: Life on the Bowery" [2001-0208], 2001 August 12; 2001 August 19; cuid34204 (Box 10, Audiocassette 718_0332)
  Duration: 1:58:28, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times; Phasing During Program
  Duplicate of 718_0547, 718_0549
- Jewish Boxer, Dmitry Salita; Mayoral Candidate Interview with Bronx Borough President Freddy Ferrer [2001-0139], 2001-08-12; cuid34205 (Box 15, Audiocassette 718_0547)
  Duration: 1:00:13
  Duplicate of 718_0332
- Orient House Demo [2001-0185], 2001-08-14 (Box 18, Item 718_0658)
- Michel Warschawski (Mikado) [2001-0187], 2001-08-14 (Box 18, Item 718_0660)
- Track 1-2: Michel Warschawski (Mikado); Track 3: Peretz Kidron [2001-0189], 2001-08-14 (Box 18, Item 718_0662)
- Gila Svirsky [2001-0199], 2001-08-14 (Box 18, Item 718_0672)
- Yatta 1 (PHR) [2001-0186], 2001-08-18 (Box 18, Item 718_0659)
- Yatta 2 (PHR) [2001-0197], 2001-08-18 (Box 18, Item 718_0670)
- Mark Green, Mayoral Candidate; Grady Turner on Flophouse: Life on Bowery [2001-0141], 2001-08-19; cuid34206 (Box 15, Audiocassette 718_0549)
  Duration: 0:57:42, Preservation Note: Digital Errors During Program; Program Distorted at Times
- Gaza 1 [2001-0200], 2001-08-19 (Box 18, Item 718_0673)
- Gaza 3 [2001-0201], 2001-08-19 (Box 18, Item 718_0674)
- W.B. with Michel Warschawski (Mikado) Check [2001-0188], 2001-08-20 (Box 18, Item 718_0661)
- Jews Who Rock with DJ Melish! [2001-0143], 2001-08-26; cuid34207 (Box 15, Audiocassette 718_0551)
  Duration: 0:59:10, Preservation Note: Static During Program
- A: Mayra Peters-Quintero and Andy Stettner on Tuv Taam Labor Dispute; Oscar Palacios, Richard Greene, Melanie Kaye/Kantrowitz, Jeremy Burton / B: Primary Preview with Norm Fruchter, Andy Stettner, Brad Lander, Kathy Goldman; Jonathan Bowles on State Budget Crisis [2001-0171], 2001-09-02; 2001-09-09; cuid2616 (Box 10, Item 718_0318, Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_614)
  Melanie Kaye/Kantrowitz, Jeremy Burton and Richard Green on the 10th anniversary of the Crown Heights riots; Maira Peters-Quintero (PRLDEF attorney), Oscar Palacios (fired worker) and Arieh Lebowitz (Jewish Labor Committee) on the efforts to organize the workers at Tuv Taam in Brooklyn. Co-host, Nan Rubin. Mayoral Primary Show on the issues, with Kathy Goldman (CFRC), Andy Stettner (JFREJ), Norman Fruchter (Institute for Education andf Social Policy, NYU), Brad Lander (Fifth Avenue Committee and ANHD); the New York State Budget with Jonathan Bowls, Center for an Urban Future.
- Tuv Taam Labor Dispute; Crown Heights Riots 10 Years [2001-0136], 2001-09-02; cuid2609 (Box 15, Item 718_0544, Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_608)
  Melanie Kaye/Kantrowitz, Jeremy Burton and Richard Green on the 10th anniversary of the Crown Heights riots; Maira Peters-Quintero (PRLDEF attorney), Oscar Palacios (fired worker) and Arieh Lebowitz (Jewish Labor Committee) on the efforts to organize the workers at Tuv Taam in Brooklyn.
  Original Format: DAT, Duration 65 min.
- Primary Elections; State Budget Crunch [2001-0135], 2001-09-09; cuid34208 (Box 15, Audiocassette 718_0543)